Row! Row faster!
If we can just get off this lake,
we'll be safe.
Ahhh!
Miaomiao, look out!
Quick, grab my hand!
It's okay now, Miaomiao.
Aaaaah!
Pull me up!
No, we can't save you.
The raft's broken.
It can't hold three.
Miaomiao!
I'm your boyfriend!
How could you do this?
The one I've always loved is Wang Kun.
I even had his child.
What?
She's right.
You stay here
and distract that monster for us.
No!
You can't!
Don't blame me!
Every year on this date,
I'll burn 10 billion for you.
I'll burn 10 billion for you!
I even had his child.
Hahaha...
What's going on?
Didn't I die?
I...
I've been reborn
back to when we first arrived on the island.
Hahaha!
Honey, you're finally awake.
You passed out
as soon as we got to the island.
That's the mouth
that said 'don't save him'.
No, we can't save him.
The raft's broken.
You must have low blood sugar.
Here, take the candy.
That's the hand that pushed me into the abyss.
Hey, hey, Kun!
There you are!
Let's go fishing in the lake.
Sounds good.
I've always heard the fish in this lake are
huge and easy to catch.
Big fish... in the lake?
Monster...
There's a monster in the lake!